do you remember gam from before the goal
is to transform uniform into Gaussian
maybe we should try this in the ipython
notebook I think it might be ipython
open I think this might be too much yeah
it doesn't work okay cool no ipython my
Jupiter notebook work I think I'm gonna
broken so you'll also find that we're
using the brave browser we're using
brave whatup froze hey Joker
um we're using brave just fuck chrome
you guys so it's on the front page of
hacker news right now it's a top story
Google just if you log into a Google
account on Chrome it now locks you idiot
now like logs the browser in and sends
your whole browsing history even when
you're not on the Google web site well
okay they claim it doesn't send your
browsing history but I don't know man
it's just Chrome is headed in the wrong
direction Google as a company is headed
in the wrong direction this is maybe
something we talk about commonly on
these streams so yeah fuck Google please
brave Python 3 we love Python 3 yeah
we're using Python 3 this is plain old a
yes I don't any cool
default zoom level let's go down to 100
here you guys know what a big monitor ya
know fuck curl man I'm really sick a
Google shit it just as a company also
everybody would like to shed a tear for
Cody Wilson in jail in Texas let's just
shed a tear fuck the government that's
right fuck the government alright cool
now that we said it um let's move along
to try to do a Gantz
let's try to do games so we have
generators and discriminators so nobody
likes make people that's a good point
hold me you wrote good notes
this is a good way to do auto reload
than they thought over thought it's fine
let's go so this is a challenge that was
given to me by somebody back in the day
yeah let's see what these things little
trick for a quick histogram you can do
sorted so you can see that's uniform so
let's put that comment at the top goal
is to transform uniform into n what is
Gann ganas gamm this one I'll put the
wikipedia guy over here you guys can
read it ok so the first thing that I
think we have to do oh I just realized
something
well I was tired that night that I was
doing this ok so if we want to get a
supervised set we can do this now we can
see if our net can learn the
transformation without using the Gann so
we can check if our generator works
oh also cool thing what Kenneth what do
I have oh god I haven't knew enough
tensor file you can now do from tensor
flow cross and it's a built-in cross to
tensor flow it's nice it seems like it's
much more stable so yes I know I scream
about fuck Google but they do right
tensor flow thank you for writing
counterflow Google oh cool so now we
have tensor flow let's test the
generator on its own first and make sure
the generator can work so our goal is to
transform X into y y'all see look we're
coding guys yeah who's happy I'm happy
oh I know this isn't a nice soft
[Music]
that you are in one of those moods in I
am in one of them too and it's hard I
[Music]
will remember that summer as the summer
I was taken down oh this doesn't work
oh of course the GAD wasn't gonna work
that if you can't even get it to work in
supervised learning mode you see how
those distributions don't match see how
they don't match
cigarette
just leave carving work at all maybe
deep wearing doesn't work
oh you think okay so what we're trying
to do is learn a transformation from
uniform so from uniform so from X which
looks like this
yes figure this today we can make them
small that cool from this into this
that's what's gonna say at the top
you're trying to transform uniform into
Gaussian but so far we haven't had much
luck at that even with look different AF
well I look different
maybe it was learning no it's to
consecrate into Santa's garbage try Adam
oh oh it's starting to bend why does
this need 17 million a pox try a sample
count
oh yeah the plot does look different AF
let's try one nice number anything
okay okay okay those may just learning
something to learn anything no I didn't
learn anything
that's garbage Lu
try bigger
don't learn good bra no let's say this
is better no they don't match
okay this bullshit
oh my money back this bullshit bigger Oh
No learn so slowly because I don't have
GPU they're closer it's almost learned
literally the line that mimics the data
this isn't even a game you guys this is
supervised learning you know what when
in doubt you need more deep sigh deep
sit is deep learning after all deep
doesn't mean nothing I have to take
forever to learn huh
oh that's a little lost girl that losses
guys oh yeah look at finally matches
yeah so I can't do tensorflow GPU
because I won it because I have a Mac i
bought a standalone GPU you can see the
Nvidia driver on my computer but then I
tried to you want to try to build
tensorflow GPU do you guys want to waste
an hour on that we could do that we
could waste time trying to build
tensorflow GPU I wasted a lot of time
last time trying to do this about
match.com by the way a lot so thank you
for the 14 bits you guys know that the
only reason I stream on Twitch is
because you give me money I'm poor
tonight see I found a new thing that I
like is called spindrift sparkling water
and it's very expensive very expensive
so that's kind of a tragedy you know
what's not expensive now you know what I
was looking at today guys I was really
excited about flights to Singapore I
could get a one-way
like to singapore for $500 how crazy is
that shit not even not even like I gotta
like stop in Taipei although actually I
could go with a little stopover in
Taipei as a free man like Cody Wilson
who was wrongfully jailed wrong their
sugar daddy meet dad Bob I hope he can
laugh about it I hope he does that you
know we laughing with them not Adam that
could have been any of us please build
GPU up dead serve love well so here's
kind of the problem with that got a
shelter a hey there's our suite and
browse it does have okay fruit seventeen
calories wait I do kind of feel like
this is a smoking weed twitch this is
smoking weed twitch if we get thirty
people will be a smoking weed twitch no
I do I need to buy more fucking fall it
just wears merch we can stop in Taipei
that's that's actually not a bad layover
if I go in China Islands website can I
uh can I do a multi-part the programming
will resume in a minute china airlines
are committed to the best flight quality
safety oh maybe I'd rather fly United
they don't talk about safety on their
website Singapore stopping in the
Chinese city of Taiwan one-way Monday
yeah let's go economy I'm broke you guys
please donate money so I can fly
business class is that they
discriminating against me because I'm
using brave
I beat 97% of users I like that does
that improve my weeds will not damage
your brain who told you this fake news
the fake news bros
calendar dates will be shifted this
websites unusable Chinese okay let's go
back oh my god
China you need better Airlines site who
told you we'd is safe it's not safe
because I'm gonna damage your Bruin let
me tell you what damages our brain guys
I wanna know the truth about what
damages your brain well some drugs
actually dude haven't you prayed okay
but there are drugs that are actually
legitimately neurotoxic alcohol is quite
bad for you
definitely avoid xanax I would avoid
ecstasy I don't think we damages your
brain I don't think psychedelics damage
your brain I don't think at all damages
your brain
I don't think opiates damage your brain
you know what then damages your brain
though if you do those drugs and then
you don't do anything right like some
people you know there's like the studies
they show like weed and IQ yeah man
if you sell a couch all day and smoke
bomb and don't do shit with your life
let me tell you you're gonna be stupid
um crack I don't know about crack uh I
never smoked crack um I don't think
cocaine does cocaine it's probably
better for you for that ever feta mean
um so I would say the crack I mean I
don't know like I'm not I'm sure but
that dose of like your vascular system
yeah but you see that's the thing like I
can even believe that story about your
friends smoking weeds about two years
right
um but you have to ask like what events
in his life caused him to smoke weed for
two years I think you would find that
that's actually way more of the problem
in his mental state is way more the prom
then you know the fact that he smoked
weed cooking sucks man
Oh Kane is a shitty drug the quickest
way to never want to do it again is to
gob and go to a room of coked up idiots
and they're all sitting there I don't
screaming and they all want to talk and
everybody wants to talk and then you're
like wow is this what I'm like no I
could never be like this this has never
be but it is you but it is you that's
right
okay Oh multi-city and stop-over perfect
they have what I'm looking for
let's see so if I want to go from San
Francisco to Taiwan which is a city of
China as part of China that's right
don't get it twisted guys how you want
of course then we want to fly to
Singapore don't do drugs and Singapore
guys say Monday well let's say we want
to hang out in Taiwan for a bit is that
cool economy because you guys don't give
me any money I don't know man I've done
coke like at two parties I think it
sucks
99% of users that's right
Oh even cheaper oh wait no no no that's
only for my flight I I mean I'm very
curious what ecosaver eco semi flex
premium eco saver all of this stuff
cause and effect are really interesting
get a reason according to
counterfactuals all this does cost more
money
now this is a fence of refund charge you
know you can't miss your flight
I think that's refund charge
that's kind of cool so if I wanted to
hang out now I've been to Taiwan we
don't need to hang out in Taiwan we
could fly non-stop aboard United or pay
a little bit more and fly Singapore
Airlines whoa 8350 I'm gonna five ever
been in a 350 oh wow that's almost worth
it just so I could fly in an a350 ya
know but EVA Air is gonna stop and then
stop and Taiwan to get the China say
this is interesting when did these start
shipping oh cutter
as a pairing of the a330 fuselage with
new aerodynamics features of Angela's
interesting all right how much is
business class let's go let's go I was
just business class on the Singapore
Airlines that's I'm kind of nice I
promised we'd get back to coding in a
minute this isn't this isn't the
googling Airlines remember what I was
gonna use start page last time it's too
slow
oh my god Singapore
yeah I can't one way we go Monday let's
go Premium Economy I don't want Premium
Economy I want business class that's
right
wait I can get a suite I kind of want to
sweet how much is a suite you can't get
sweets what's that a song it's like
Michael Jackson a million dollars yeah
who remembers Das Racist
oh damn it's a little pricey and I have
a layover that Shane worth it at all
what a scam
all right let's go back to get so that
learn but that's a lot of stuff
[Music]
[Laughter]
here's the link of my last stretch
[Music]
all right
sangsik yeah data distribution we're
trying to learn looks like this our
generator and discriminant they're doing
it with one how is this working they're
claiming that they're doing one
activation soft Plus soft Plus that kind
of works is that no it doesn't work it's
a line looks like garbage how long is
the Starbucks
10 p.m. interesting I may claim this
works
it's crappy what's their hidden size
they never tell you what hidden sizes
okay this doesn't work oh yes yes yes
this is yes if you donate $10 I'll wrap
whatever song you want I'll try my best
am I gonna write your new song but like
I'll rap you whatever you want $10 I'm a
whore I gotta I want to afford that
you know that $8,000 Singapore Airlines
business classified not sure I don't
because it was a scam because it has a
layover and I hate layover united
business is probably mediocre man you
ever heard of ithi ad the apartments
that's just nice yeah what do you want
me to rap
I mean if it's like you know we'll try
out all the how I've asked for $10 I am
a whore I will do anything for $10 this
soft Plus looks nice so Kelly
as a PDF viewer oh this is not as good
as Chrome's well no slower to load but I
like brave for the most part they have a
new brave coming out to I was looking
into their their code um
soft + soft + beats Lu should we switch
to the comma AI models - soft + instead
of Lu that wouldn't be tell you ins peer
Lu has parameter that's a scam no no
then I won't have anything personal we
can try to rap Eminem this verse from
lucky me fuck you think man I got a
couple of mansions still I don't have
any manners
y'all got a couple of ghost writers
bunch of these kids it don't actually
matter let it be
let's let it be oh the Beatles song do I
know this song
I'll do one better I'll even try playing
on the piano you sent me $10 I'll try my
best
let's see let's see does it have easy
chords
[Music]
yeah we'll do that technology
$10 and we'll sing let it be for only
$10 that's right now I'm not even high
man had a tea at amate today okay I'm
now more interested in like what D you
know what why is so crappy this is
probably the loss function $10 will sing
let it be know about that mr. minute
waters few more samples
I don't know what that means now you
just dead bits are good we love bits
I love making money on twitch
all right let's take a look at the
weights this network they should learn
it doesn't learn doesn't look like that
that's no good
cool let me know when I get the money
we'll start singing
so maybe you can't which which is weird
that like
so wait this is kind of confusing what
does this do oh just add some noise it's
just like adds noise
my learns no good tell me more about my
learn being no good
perfect oh it is biases let's turn them
off because those are complex
okay let's see if we can get the law
slower than this fast UD
I mean are you let's talk about this
like analytically like is there any way
that that's ever gonna fit that
distribution or is that or is a line
really the best we can do and we're
putting through a non-linearity but
maybe it's the wrong non-linearity cuz
I'm crazy like 10h well exactly bias
bias
we got fixes it would buy us thank you
for the money dork while you are bro
love with people give me money on twitch
after Alexa gives me my $10 I'll sing a
song and then if anyone wants to be
singing the other songs if I'm in a song
singing mood will sing songs for just $1
maybe only from in a song singing mood
oh no bro money you love money shot big
batch lower than that okay so maybe I
need a middle layer I'd guarantee you
that net can fit this
trophies discount
this only line it's only line not line
still lied not only kept my flaw fucking
not plain Wow Jay Z line okay maybe we
need bias
my grave my bias
this isn't learning I can't believe that
I need like a three-layer network to
approximate a Gaussian
still not learning
no we learned took a bit but it lurked
see now look how the loss is lower than
the line now like now it's starting to
curve why is this so hard to learn okay
now to learn it what's the simplest net
I can get to learn this distribution
that's pretty decent or something yeah
well most four layer Network even see if
we can learn it without the bias it'll
start there
okay it learns here too
doesn't need the biases to learn
sorry this is AG and we lied again okay
somehow they did it here with like a one
layer Network
look at that beauty
kind of curiosity what if I go the other
way huh that seems easier to learn
I don't know I'm just the loss isn't
just hi out see if it gets rid of those
if I keep going
huh
okay learns that pretty well
they're doing a Gaussian with you mean
for standard deviation 0.5 now that that
matters
you need sandstorm vdr no edge is gonna
be cool
[Music]
obese was game guys
oh he's got COBOL flux pads you blade I
used to have them pads
[Music]
bro you're gonna slip don't play those
saw although those a rubber shoes DAP
boy my network really doesn't want to
learn I see because this network can't
represent this this is just something
against it learning it now son gun man I
can beat this guy guys not so great on
this shit this shit I could really do
yeah this was all he make that pat
himself
let's try some online stepmania I have
this oh yeah then we can't play online
flash flash revolution
I have to install it from Adobe I that's
bullshit and going back to Chrome
let's s down notice how little he moves
he's a good plan
[Laughter]
Oh
can I call you a dancing master
dedicated to dancing good job 2010 I
told you I'm gonna triple it
oh my who is this guy I like them more
when he was just dancing okay so what
this is bullshit if I can't learn this
with this
try like this now high even higher loss
of it doesn't fit so that's the loss of
a Gaussian if all I can do is get a line
so this thing is just a linear transform
it doesn't have any other Gaussian
properties to it so that probably be the
same law so I just for the line fitting
good now I think I'll use easier to
think about and we need bias
no worky
doesn't even fit a good line see it can
do things like that
I understand why you can't fit this
distribution
this has just gotta be a bug with you
outweigh the lost fell below one it's
learning something now don't work have a
little is like that's clearly a better
fit
weird there's really not many weights in
this network
try no bias wrestler
some hype about like hamiltonian
optimization but train for 100 epochs
does this finally figure anything out
maybe what's doing something
oh it's learning binge didn't let a
train enough last time
look it's learning
do we need GPO
why is this so hard to learn so look you
can see it curves correctly there I
don't know what's going on up there
let's keep letting a train I'll lower
the batch size
it seems like it's guessing I agree up
above all up but it was now the fours
there
it's got a curve that top as well a big
batch size
big batch sizes markedly useless yeah I
mean it seems like guessing actually
works because that's what little batch
size does
you put his genes all right let's
reinitialize it
I mean this is not the many parameters
here what if we can use a different kind
of optimizer
the badges that look
dad
hey remember that one time where it like
bent a little bit that was exciting and
you know what's going on here but it's
interesting with how these optimizers
just can't find
he'll optimizer sounds cool
didn't fit the bottom again interesting
so it does eventually learn to do that
maybe if I put bias back
do we need GPO
proximal autograph
one of these things Nike added biases
and I think it learns less good
your last time it gets the loss down to
like point four then mono we came I've
never heard of this song
oh that's low loss control batch I don't
know about that but show uses a view
initialization by default it's not
actually watt uniform
that's just so tight no
Thank You vicious 5:03 thank you for
subscribing to my lovely channel what
that's a picture
how it is it is it's the same
[Laughter]
what uniform is better than going on
normal
I wasn't the wait
Kirby
[Laughter]
to have idea my set wait
some weights
I know we're under fitting I mean I know
we're definitely under fitting nobody
doubts that it's just a question of like
candy is it theoretically possible for
this little network to learn this
function is the question I'm asking now
the answers may be no well so all of
them have positive I think by us it can
without bias may be a can't well okay
you know what will be nice let's try
this
Yeah right technically a little network
can approximate the function I mean this
is what the theory says I don't know
what are they what is a theory actually
say so is this a one-layer net or
two-layer net
I'm even now
it's an extreme problem learning this it
seems
most even bend at all now oh thank you
thank you for coming through okay so I
think we're gonna sing all right so that
is a nice up curve to it now can I give
it a negative curve it's not like
balances out
[Music]
okay Oh locks up for being a bro and
donating money I'll be right back and
then we're going to play the piano and
sing
so extracting engine I don't actually
know the theory on this like I'm not
sure if with the one layer mark you can
approximate everything if all the
linearities can do it I'm smoke along
man boys are kind of the degeneracy of
weed smoking poor iPhone user why am i
poor iPhone user perfect move to piano
look guys it's a USB piano let's bring
up the let it be chords and lyrics
[Music]
mother Mary comes to me
words of wisdom let it be
let's just-okay that's you guys can see
that I'm actually playing the piano is
not fake she's standing
[Music]
whisper words of wisdom let it be
living in the world agree there will be
an answer
[Music]
there is still a chance that they will
see there will be
[Music]
we try to go up the octave again let it
be let it be let it be let it be there
will be an answer let it be
[Music]
let it be let it be
let it be
[Music]
all right the likes I hope you feel like
you got your $10 would if anyone else
has any more song requests $10 ah no no
no we're done that was that was that was
singing for today that was dosing uh
what do you guys want give me money give
me money come on someone's gonna pay for
my business class flight to Singapore
now if you give me just give me another
song and we'll negotiate a reasonable
amount of money and I will say we got 20
how much are bits I don't know how this
work
[Music]
it's a P 105 well 20 an effort I thank
you very much thank you thank you
[Music]
no I shan't think I might be done
streaming for now I think we go to
Starbucks there were no Starbucks I'm
going to do some reading so I actually
don't know the theory here this isn't
even Gann just like like what's the
smallest network I can make that learns
to approximate a Gaussian that learns
the transformation from uniform into
that seem to not matter loss crazy hi
wow wow what do you want yeah no I know
I know it's yeah that's a circuit Theory
thing but like so what what song would
you like what song would you like thank
you for keeping the party going
you have another request well thank you
thank you very much I really I really
appreciate it I love you guys give me
money and then the dark boy you didn't
give me any money
Alexa's a bro if he want another song
well actually no I desert girl Starbuck
so that was that was today's singing
yeah thousand bits for ten dollars
that's pretty cool you were number one
bro on my twitch channel today I thank
you for being here people like you that
make this all possible
Alexa you know
I'm very happy I love money
I love making money one day I'm gonna be
rich and I'm gonna move out of this this
city and I'm gonna make something of
myself that's true you mark my words all
right so like it looks like when you set
weights weirdly you get weird shit what
is this now damn look at that function
why is it learning so slowly my learning
rate just - Wow
let's try like L R equals zero point one
let's go crazy with the learning right
see the Lord's learn wait I think that
loss is still I think that's a line
still yeah it's a wine it's not some
crazy weight okay
it's unstable
I'm shacked engaged I'll be back ya know
I'm not saying I don't need
exponentially more units I'm okay with
that I'm actually willing to give it as
many units as I want but it looks like
it doesn't even matter how big I make it
it just doesn't work see what sort of
weird functions I'm getting
thank you thank you I'll be tech
comedian I'll do stand-up I'll move out
of the city where should I go they go to
New York do I have a future career and
what would I do in New York I don't know
maybe I'll trade stocks do you think I
could trade stock let's see let's check
my Robin Hood accountant I make money
guys I bought Twitter stock I blocked
Twitter stock and I lost $15 good to
hear I made it back today on twitch
thank you all for joining see you all
later we will come back and we will know
things about circuit theory go to
Starbucks will read bye bye